export default[
  {
    question: "What school does Harry Potter attend?",
    options: ["Hogwarts", "Beauxbatons", "Durmstrang", "Ilvermorny"],
    answer: "Hogwarts",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the headmaster of the school Harry attends?",
    options: [
      "Albus Dumbledore",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Minerva McGonagall",
      "Dolores Umbridge",
    ],
    answer: "Albus Dumbledore",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Harry Potter's greatest enemy?",
    options: [
      "Lord Voldemort",
      "Draco Malfoy",
      "Lucius Malfoy",
      "Bellatrix Lestrange",
    ],
    answer: "Lord Voldemort",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Harry Potter's closest friend (male)?",
    options: [
      "Ron Weasley",
      "Neville Longbottom",
      "Draco Malfoy",
      "Seamus Finnigan",
    ],
    answer: "Ron Weasley",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Harry Potter's closest friend (female)?",
    options: [
      "Hermione Granger",
      "Ginny Weasley",
      "Luna Lovegood",
      "Cho Chang",
    ],
    answer: "Hermione Granger",
  },
  {
    question: "What game, using flying broomsticks, is played by wizards?",
    options: ["Quidditch", "Gobstones", "Wizard Chess", "Exploding Snap"],
    answer: "Quidditch",
  },
  {
    question: "What teacher, despised by many, teaches potions?",
    options: [
      "Severus Snape",
      "Horace Slughorn",
      "Gilderoy Lockhart",
      "Remus Lupin",
    ],
    answer: "Severus Snape",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of animal is Harry's pet?",
    options: ["Owl", "Cat", "Rat", "Toad"],
    answer: "Owl",
  },
  {
    question: "Who tells Harry that he is, in fact, a wizard?",
    options: ["Hagrid", "Dumbledore", "McGonagall", "Sirius Black"],
    answer: "Hagrid",
  },
  {
    question: "Who wrote the Harry Potter series?",
    options: [
      "J.K. Rowling",
      "Stephen King",
      "J.R.R. Tolkien",
      "George R.R. Martin",
    ],
    answer: "J.K. Rowling",
  },
  {
    question: "In what country are the books set?",
    options: ["United Kingdom", "United States", "France", "Germany"],
    answer: "United Kingdom",
  },
  {
    question: "What platform does the train to the school depart from?",
    options: ["9 3/4", "8 3/4", "10", "7 1/2"],
    answer: "9 3/4",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of creature is Dobby?",
    options: ["House elf", "Goblin", "Giant", "Troll"],
    answer: "House elf",
  },
  {
    question: "What house is Draco Malfoy a part of?",
    options: ["Slytherin", "Gryffindor", "Ravenclaw", "Hufflepuff"],
    answer: "Slytherin",
  },
  {
    question: "What prison does Sirius Black escape from?",
    options: ["Azkaban", "Nurmengard", "Azkadell", "Shawshank"],
    answer: "Azkaban",
  },
  {
    question: "In Quidditch, what is Harry Potter's position?",
    options: ["Seeker", "Chaser", "Beater", "Keeper"],
    answer: "Seeker",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Harry's mother's name?",
    options: [
      "Lily Potter",
      "Petunia Dursley",
      "Molly Weasley",
      "Alice Longbottom",
    ],
    answer: "Lily Potter",
  },
  {
    question: "What house has the house colour of blue?",
    options: ["Ravenclaw", "Hufflepuff", "Gryffindor", "Slytherin"],
    answer: "Ravenclaw",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is George Weasley's twin?",
    options: ["Fred", "Ron", "Percy", "Bill"],
    answer: "Fred",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Harry's pet?",
    options: ["Hedwig", "Crookshanks", "Scabbers", "Trevor"],
    answer: "Hedwig",
  },
  {
    question: "What are Tom Riddle's diary and Rowena Ravenclaw's diadem?",
    options: ["Horcruxes", "Hallows", "Portkeys", "Pensieves"],
    answer: "Horcruxes",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What creature, from the Chamber of Secrets, paralyzes and kills students in Harry's second year?",
    options: ["Basilisk", "Acromantula", "Dementor", "Werewolf"],
    answer: "Basilisk",
  },
  {
    question: "Who dies during the Triwizard Tournament?",
    options: [
      "Cedric Diggory",
      "Viktor Krum",
      "Fleur Delacour",
      "Harry Potter",
    ],
    answer: "Cedric Diggory",
  },
  {
    question: "What will 'suck all the happiness from you'?",
    options: ["Dementor", "Boggart", "Vampire", "Werewolf"],
    answer: "Dementor",
  },
  {
    question: "Who haunts the girls' bathroom?",
    options: [
      "Moaning Myrtle",
      "Nearly Headless Nick",
      "The Grey Lady",
      "The Fat Friar",
    ],
    answer: "Moaning Myrtle",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has radish earrings?",
    options: [
      "Luna Lovegood",
      "Hermione Granger",
      "Ginny Weasley",
      "Cho Chang",
    ],
    answer: "Luna Lovegood",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the spell 'Alohomora' do?",
    options: ["Unlocks", "Lights up", "Levitate", "Heals"],
    answer: "Unlocks",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Voldemort's snake?",
    options: ["Nagini", "Aragog", "Fluffy", "Norbert"],
    answer: "Nagini",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the mischievous poltergeist that wreaks havoc throughout the school?",
    options: [
      "Peeves",
      "Nearly Headless Nick",
      "The Bloody Baron",
      "The Fat Friar",
    ],
    answer: "Peeves",
  },
  {
    question: "What ball does the school hold?",
    options: ["Yule Ball", "Christmas Ball", "Summer Ball", "Halloween Ball"],
    answer: "Yule Ball",
  },
];
